learnlakenona.com 2019-07-06

# Privacy Policy | Lake Nona

PRIVACY POLICY OF LAKENONA.COM  
Lake Nona Property Holdings, LLC and its affiliates (collectively referred to as “Lake Nona”) respect your privacy. We strive to use information to provide the best possible service while respecting the confidentiality of information we are entrusted with. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we may receive or collect when you use our services, as well as some of the methods we use to safeguard your personal information.

  COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND COOKIES  
We may from time to time collect personal information in order to understand your specific needs and serve you better. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, email address, or phone number. Lake Nona may use cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our website and services. A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser. While most browsers accept cookies by default, you can manually set your browser to refuse all cookies, accept cookies from specific websites, or highlight when a cookie is sent to your browser. Lake Nona’s servers may also automatically record information when you visit our website, including the URL that directed you to our website, your IP address, browser type and the date and time of your visit.

There are two main types of cookies:  
• Session cookies: These are temporary cookies that expire at the end of a browser session (when you leave the site). Session cookies allow the website to recognize you as you navigate between pages during a single browser session and allow you to use the website most efficiently.  
• Persistent cookies: In contrast to session cookies, persistent cookies are stored on your equipment between browsing sessions until expiration or deletion. They enable the website to “recognize” you upon your return.

We may use session cookies to:  
• Help us maintain security and verify your details as you use our website.  
We may use persistent cookies to:  
• Collect and compile anonymous, aggregated information for statistical and evaluation purposes to help us understand how users use the website and help us improve our website.

In addition to cookies which send information to us, we may also use cookies which collect information and send it to third parties. An example of this is Google Analytics. Please check any relevant third-party website for more information about its use of cookies which may differ from ours.  
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. However, you have the ability to disable cookies if you wish, generally through changing your internet browser settings.

  HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION  
The information Lake Nona collects is used to comprehensively understand your needs and interests, and permit Lake Nona to deliver a more consistent and personalized experience. For example, Lake Nona may use your information to:  
• communicate with you about products and services;  
• provide service and support;  
• update you about new services;  
• provide personalized promotional offers;  
• select content to be communicated to you; and  
• contact you for market research regarding Lake Nona’s services.  
Your information may be aggregated with other clients’ information on a purely non-identifiable basis to understand how our products and services are used.

  CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS AND PRIVACY  
The California Online Privacy Protection Act applies to residents of California. California residents may request to review and request changes to information collected.  To request this type of information, please contact us at the address or email listed in the Contact Us paragraph below.

  GLOBAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR) AND PRIVACY  
The GDPR applies to residents of Europe. In accordance with the GDPR, you have the right to request from us any personal information we have retained about you and the right to request we delete that information and stop sending you communications, or that we correct any personal information that you believe is not accurate.  Please contact us about your personal information at info@lakenona.com.  
By submitting your personal information to us, you agree to the transfer, storage, use and processing of your personal information outside the country of your residence, including the U.S.

  POLICY ON SHARING YOUR INFORMATION  
Lake Nona will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others.  Lake Nona may share personal information with companies working on our behalf and Lake Nona affiliate entities for the purposes detailed above. In any such cases, however, we require that the companies or entities adhere to privacy standards and policies at least as restrictive as those Lake Nona has in place.  
Circumstances may arise, whether for strategic or other business reasons, in which Lake Nona decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in various countries. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or, conversely, the receipt of such personal information from sellers. It is Lake Nona’s established practice to seek appropriate protection for all personal information in advance of any such transaction.  
We may make use of your information when we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to: (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or legitimate governmental request, (b) detect, prevent, or otherwise address suspected fraud, security or technical issues, (c) enforce any applicable Terms and Conditions, including investigation of potential violations thereof, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Lake Nona, its users or the general public as required or permitted by law.

  SITES COVERED BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
The Lake Nona website (www. LakeNona.com) may from time-to-time link to third-party websites for your convenience and to provide easy access to additional useful information. Should you select such a link, you will leave the Lake Nona website. Lake Nona does not control these sites nor their privacy practices, which may differ from Lake Nona’s practices and policies. Any personal data you choose to provide to or that is collected by such third parties is not in any way covered by the Privacy Policy of LakeNona.com. We recommend that you read over such website’s privacy policy before providing any personal information. A link to another website from LakeNona.com does not constitute an endorsement or representation about the value, quality or usefulness of anything found on that third-party website.

  ACCESS TO AND ACCURACY OF YOUR INFORMATION  
Lake Nona strives to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. Toward this goal we may utilize various technologies, management processes and policies. As part of our overall data accuracy initiative, Lake Nona provides you with reasonable access to your personal information so you may review and correct your information if needed. To safeguard your privacy and security, we may verify your identity through various means, such as by requiring a password and user ID, before granting access to your data, if applicable.  We ask that you update your information as and when it changes so any information used to serve you remains as accurate as possible.

  KEEPING YOUR INFORMATION SECURE  
Lake Nona values your trust and takes it seriously. To prevent unauthorized access and disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of your information, Lake Nona utilizes industry standard physical, technical and administrative procedures to safeguard any personal information we may collect.

  CHANGES TO THIS POLICY  
The effective date of this policy is May 25, 2018.  However, the world of technology changes quickly. If and when there are future changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post them at www.LakeNona.com/privacy-policy.

  CONTACT US  
We value your opinions and suggestions. Please email us with any questions or concerns at info@lakenona.com, or alternately you can write to us at the following address:

Lake Nona Property Holdings, LLC  
6900 Tavistock Lakes Blvd., Suite 200  
Orlando, FL 32827

  © Lake Nona Property Holdings, LLC, 2018. All rights reserved.
